Bernadette, your character
is the healer in our group.
ln charge of healing all of us,
not just Howard.
(Bernadette:)Can't help it.
My Howie-wowie has an owie. Ha, ha.
(Sheldon:)That is the most sickeningly sweet thing
l have ever experienced.
(Sheldon:)And I am sipping Kool-Aid
through a Red Vine.
Sheldon, l've got a bone to pick with you,
and I'll do it in front of all your friends.
(Penny:)Yeah, you pick that bone.
You pick that bone clean.
(Amy:)I'm gonna publicly shame you
and then sit back...
(Amy:)...as societal pressure compels you
to modify your behavior.
(Penny:)Oh, burn!
(Amy:)If you don't start treating me better,
I'm leaving you...
...for a miniature-horse breeder
named Armin.
- Armin who?
- Armin... Damn it.
(Penny:)Sheldon, she wanted to show you off to
her family and you stood her up, okay?
l mean, look at this adorable,
smushy face.